♪ Like a model like me ♪
(upbeat music)
♪ Speaking of him ♪
♪ I'm free, I'm free, I'm free, I'm free, I'm free ♪
in my day
(upbeat music)
♪ Then let's begin ♪
(rock music)
I will give you more
(upbeat music)
Bye, Miss Her.
♪ I'll give you my ♪
I don't know my head
You can be more
(upbeat music)
So they'll see
♪ In trouble ♪
♪ You'll be seen ♪
Who can you?
(upbeat music)
♪ I can't think so then ♪
I don't know
(upbeat music)
You're almost done, you're almost done.
♪ Looks like you're here ♪
I'm the one.
♪ Give you one ♪
(upbeat music)
♪ You're hoping next time ♪
It's a fun one.
♪ Let me catch the day ♪
Bye for me
(upbeat music)
♪ The terror from the ♪
♪ Last to last ♪
♪ You're like a child ♪
♪ This is the chance ♪
(upbeat music)
♪ 'Cause you're your ♪
Finally!
(upbeat music)
♪ Do you have love ♪
♪ You know I love you ♪
Thanks for watching!
(upbeat music)
♪ Such a thing ♪
Thanks for watching!
(upbeat music)
Exciting!
It's a truth and...
(upbeat music)
♪ 'Cause I know ♪
♪ I can make it ♪
(upbeat music)
♪ Tell me what you do ♪
Trust me, I-
(upbeat music)
♪ Can you ask me ♪
♪ You're what you mean ♪
(upbeat music)